<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<chapter title='Angles and Intersecting Lines'>
    <lesson title='Angles'>
        <body>Angle: When two rays begin at a common point, a geometric figure is formed. The space between such rays, measured in degrees (°), is the angle.\n
            a. Zero Angle: Such an angle is formed when two rays completely overlap with each other (0°).\n
            b. Right Angle: This angle is formed when the space between two rays is 90°. It is similar to the corner of a square. It is usually represented by a small square between the lines.\n
            c. Straight Angle: This angle is formed when the space between two rays is 180°. This means that the rays start at a common point, but extend in directly opposite directions.\n
            d. Full Angle: If we continue to increase the space between two rays that start at a common point, there will come a time when they overlap with each other. When this happens, the angle is 360°.\n
            e. Acute Angle: It is an angle that is more than 0° but less than 90°.\n
            f. Obtuse Angle: It is an angle that is more than 90° but less than 180°.\n
            g. Reflex Angle: It is an angle that is more than 180° but less than 360°.\n
        </body>
        <test>
            !types: MCQ = Multiple Choice, Check -> Check Boxes, Text -> Free response.:
            <question number='1' type='MCQ'>
                <image>c2_l1_q1.png</image>
                <responses>Acute,Right,Obtuse</responses>
                <answer>2</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='2' type='MCQ'>
                <image>c2_l1_q2.png</image>
                <responses>Acute,Right,Obtuse</responses>
                <answer>1</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='3' type='MCQ'>
                <image>c2_l1_q3.png</image>
                <responses>Acute,Right,Obtuse</responses>
                <answer>3</answer>
            </question>
        </test>
    </lesson>
    <lesson title='Intersecting Lines'>
        <body>Intersecting Lines: Two lines that meet at a single point are known as intersecting lines. They have various unique properties, including ones that relate to the angles formed when they meet.\n
            a. Vertical Angles: Vertical Angles are the angles opposite each other when two lines intersect. They are always equal.\n
            b. Complementary Angles: Two angles that sum to 90°.\n
            c. Supplementary Angles: Two angles that sum to 180°.\n
        </body>
        <test>
            !types: MCQ = Multiple Choice, Check -> Check Boxes, Text -> Free response
            <question number='1' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l2_q1.png</image>
                <answer>156</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='2' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l2_q2.png</image>
                <answer>-7</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='3' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l2_q3.png</image>
                <answer>70</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='4' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l2_q4.png</image>
                <answer>38</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='5' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l2_q5.png</image>
                <answer>49</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='6' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l2_q6.png</image>
                <answer>47</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='7' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l2_q7.png</image>
                <answer>48</answer>
            </question>
        </test>
    </lesson>
    <lesson title='Parallel Lines'>
        <body>Parallel Lines: Two lines that never intersect are known as parallel lines.\n
            a. When a line intersects two other lines (which are parallel), the angles formed are identical on either of the parallel lines. For example: If there are two parallel lines, and a third one intersects both of them, a pair of vertical angles formed on the first line will be identical to the corresponding pair of vertical angles formed on the second line.\n
        </body>
        <test>
            !types: MCQ = Multiple Choice, Check -> Check Boxes, Text -> Free response
            <question number='1' type='MCQ'>
                <image>c2_l3_q1.png</image>
                <responses>134,46,44,124</responses>
                <answer>1</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='2' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l3_q2.png</image>
                <answer>122</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='3' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l3_q3.png</image>
                <answer>132</answer>
            </question>
            <question number='4' type='Text'>
                <image>c2_l3_q4.png</image>
                <responses>49,28,131,156</responses>
                <answer>3</answer>
            </question>
        </test>
    </lesson>
</chapter>